var robertsonTasks = [
  {
		"Num": "Tutorial",
		"XAxis": "PCs",
		"YAxis": "Population",
		"Question": "Select two continents where most countries have had rapid growth in PC's, but only modest growth in population.",
		"AnswerType": "continent",
		"AnswerCount": "2",
		"Answers": "Europe, North America, Oceania",
		"Tutorial": "true",
	},
	{
		"Num": "Tutorial2",
		"XAxis": "PCs",
		"YAxis": "GDPPerCapita",
		"Question": "Select one country in Europe that has had poor growth in PC's.",
		"AnswerType": "country",
		"AnswerCount": "1",
		"Answers": "Ukraine",
		"Tutorial": "true",
	},
	{
		"Num": "Tutorial3",
		"XAxis": "PCs",
		"YAxis": "GDPPerCapita",
		"Question": "Select three countries with very rapid growth spurt in the number of PCs per persons.",
		"AnswerType": "country",
		"AnswerCount": "3",
		"Answers": "Denmark, Iceland, Norway, Sweden, United States, Australia",
		"Tutorial": "true",
	},
	{
		"Num": "T1",
		"XAxis": "EnergyConsumption",
		"YAxis": "GDPPerCapita",
		"Question": "Select 3 countries whose rate of energy consumption was faster than their rate of GDP per capita growth.",
		"AnswerType": "country",
		"AnswerCount": "3",
		"Answers": "India, China, US", 
	},
	{
		"Num": "T2",
		"XAxis": "EnergyConsumption",
		"YAxis": "GDPPerCapita",
		"Question": "Select 2 countries with significant decreases in energy consumption.",
		"AnswerType": "country",
		"AnswerCount": "2",
		"Answers": "Russia, Ukraine", 
	},
	{
		"Num": "T3",
		"XAxis": "EnergyConsumption",
		"YAxis": "GDPPerCapita",
		"Question": "Which country had the most significant decrease in GDP per capita?",
		"AnswerType": "country",
		"AnswerCount": "1",
		"Answers": "Croatia", 
	},
	{
		"Num": "T4",
		"XAxis": "EnergyConsumption",
		"YAxis": "GDPPerCapita",
		"Question": "Which continent had the most significant increase in GDP per capita (i.e., the continent with largest percentage of countries with significant increases in GDP).",
		"AnswerType": "continent",
		"AnswerCount": "1",
		"Answers": "Europe", 
	},
	{
		"Num": "T5",
		"XAxis": "EnergyConsumption",
		"YAxis": "GDPPerCapita",
		"Question": "Select 2 countries whose GDPPerCaptia increased first, then decreased later.",
		"AnswerType": "country",
		"AnswerCount": "2",
		"Answers": "Russia, Ukraine", 
	},
	{
		"Num": "T6",
		"XAxis": "EnergyConsumption",
		"YAxis": "GDPPerCapita",
		"Question": "Which continent had the least changes in GDP per capita?",
		"AnswerType": "continent",
		"AnswerCount": "1",
		"Answers": "Africa", 
	},
	{
		"Num": "T7",
		"XAxis": "EnergyConsumption",
		"YAxis": "GDPPerCapita",
		"Question": "Which country had the most change in GDP per capita?",
		"AnswerType": "country",
		"AnswerCount": "1",
		"Answers": "Norway", 
	},
	{
		"Num": "T8",
		"XAxis": "EnergyConsumption",
		"YAxis": "GDPPerCapita",
		"Question": "Which 2 continents had the most significant increase in GDP per capita (i.e., contents with the highest percentage of countries with significant increases)?",
		"AnswerType": "continent",
		"AnswerCount": "2",
		"Answers": "Europe, North America, Oceania", 
	},
	{
		"Num": "T9",
		"XAxis": "InfantMortality",
		"YAxis": "GDPperCapita",
		"Question": "Select 3 countries with a high InfantMortality rate despite their high GDP.",
		"AnswerType": "country",
		"AnswerCount": "3",
		"Answers": "Saudi Arabia, Azerbaijan, South Africa", 
	},
	{
		"Num": "T10",
		"XAxis": "InfantMortality",
		"YAxis": "GDPperCapita",
		"Question": "What continent had the least change in InfantMortality, whose GDP was changing significantly?",
		"AnswerType": "continent",
		"AnswerCount": "1",
		"Answers": "Europe", 
	},
	{
		"Num": "T11",
		"XAxis": "LifeExpectance-Both",
		"YAxis": "InfantMortality",
		"Question": "Select two countries with decreasing InfantMortality, but little change in life expectancy.",
		"AnswerType": "country",
		"AnswerCount": "2",
    "Answers": "Azerbaijan,Hungary",
    "Notes": "Hungary is hard to see"
	},
	{
		"Num": "T12",
		"XAxis": "LifeExpectance-Both",
		"YAxis": "InfantMortality",
		"Question": "Select a country where InfantMortality fell significantly, then increased significantly.",
		"AnswerType": "country",
		"AnswerCount": "1",
		"Answers": "Liberia", 
	},
	{
		"Num": "T13",
		"XAxis": "LifeExpectance-Both",
		"YAxis": "InfantMortality",
		"Question": "Select two countries whose InfantMortality dropped first, then increased later.",
		"AnswerType": "country",
		"AnswerCount": "2",
		"Answers": "Liberia,Rwanda", 
	},
	{
		"Num": "T14",
		"XAxis": "LifeExpectance-Both",
		"YAxis": "InfantMortality",
		"Question": "Select the 2 countries whose InfantMortality fell the most.",
		"AnswerType": "country",
		"AnswerCount": "2",
		"Answers": "Gambia,India,Saudi Arabia", 
	},
	{
		"Num": "T15",
		"XAxis": "LifeExpectance-Both",
		"YAxis": "InfantMortality",
		"Question": "Which continent had the least changes in InfantMortality?",
		"AnswerType": "continent",
		"AnswerCount": "1",
		"Answers": "Europe", 
	},
	{
		"Num": "T16",
		"XAxis": "LifeExpectance-Both",
		"YAxis": "InfantMortality",
		"Question": "Which continent had the least changes in Life Expectancy?",
		"AnswerType": "continent",
		"AnswerCount": "1",
		"Answers": "Europe", 
	},
	{
		"Num": "T17",
		"XAxis": "EnergyConsumption",
		"YAxis": "Population",
		"Question": "Select 2 countries whose population grew faster than their rate of energy consumption?",
		"AnswerType": "country",
		"AnswerCount": "2",
		"Answers": "India, China", 
	},
	{
		"Num": "T18",
		"XAxis": "EnergyConsumption",
		"YAxis": "Population",
		"Question": "Select 3 countries whose rate of population growth was much slower than their rate of energy consumption other than United States.",
		"AnswerType": "country",
		"AnswerCount": "3",
		"Answers": "Canada, France, Japan, Korea", 
	},
	{
		"Num": "T19",
		"XAxis": "LifeExpectance-Women",
		"YAxis": "LifeExpectance-Men",
		"Question": "What country had a significant reversal from increases in life expectancy to decreases?",
		"AnswerType": "country",
		"AnswerCount": "1",
		"Answers": "Liberia, Rwanda", 
	},
	{
		"Num": "T20",
		"XAxis": "LifeExpectance-Women",
		"YAxis": "LifeExpectance-Men",
		"Question": "What country tends to have men's life expectancy decreasing faster than women's life expectancy?",
		"AnswerType": "country",
		"AnswerCount": "1",
		"Answers": "Russia", 
	},
	{
		"Num": "T21",
		"XAxis": "LifeExpectance-Both",
		"YAxis": "GDPPerCapita",
		"Question": "Which continent has the lowest life expectancy?",
		"AnswerType": "continent",
		"AnswerCount": "1",
		"Answers": "Africa", 
	},
	{
		"Num": "T22",
		"XAxis": "LifeExpectance-Both",
		"YAxis": "GDPPerCapita",
		"Question": "To which continent do countries that have had a decrease followed by increase in GDP belong?",
		"AnswerType": "continent",
		"AnswerCount": "1",
		"Answers": "Europe", 
	},
	{
		"Num": "T23",
		"XAxis": "ArableArea",
		"YAxis": "Population",
		"Question": "What large (population over 100 million)countries have seen a decrease in their ArableArea, even as their population increases?",
		"AnswerType": "country",
		"AnswerCount": "2",
		"Answers": "Russia, USA", 
	},
	{
		"Num": "T24",
		"XAxis": "ArableArea",
		"YAxis": "Population",
		"Question": "What country had a significant overall increases in ArableArea, but only slight increases in population?",
		"AnswerType": "country",
		"AnswerCount": "1",
		"Answers": "Australia", 
  }
];

module.exports = robertsonTasks;